As the relentless pace of technology continues to advance, companies must adapt or get left behind.
随着科技以势不可挡的速度持续发展，公司必须适应，否则就会被甩在后面。
One of the key areas of contention these days is the driverless car.
如今，一个关键的竞争领域是无人驾驶汽车。
Autonomous cars have long been featured in science fiction movies and books, but in recent years they have moved from a pipe dream to a reality.
自动驾驶汽车长期以来一直出现在科幻电影和书籍中，但近年来，它们已经从一个不切实际的幻想变成了现实。
The development of the autonomous car actually started in the 1920s, but it wasn't until the 1980s that the first prototypes were successfully created, one of which was designed by Mercedes-Benz.
自动驾驶汽车的发展实际上始于20世纪20年代，但直到20世纪80年代，第一批原型车才成功制造出来，其中一辆是由梅赛德斯-奔驰设计的。
Since then the technology has gone from strength to strength and these days many companies are jumping on the bandwagon.
从那以后，这项技术不断发展壮大，如今许多公司都在跟风赶时髦。
Uber is the latest to announce its plan to unroll a fleet of driverless cars.
优步最近宣布推出无人驾驶汽车车队计划。
It follows Apple and Ford, who have announced similar plans, and Google and Tesla, who already have autonomous cars on the road.
在此之前，苹果和福特也宣布了类似的计划，而谷歌和特斯拉已经有自动驾驶汽车在路上行驶了。
Two questions arise: Do we really need them?
由此产生了两个问题：我们真的需要它们吗？
And are they really safe?
它们真的安全吗？
Advocates of driverless cars would argue 'yes' to both.
无人驾驶汽车的倡导者对这两个问题都会回答“是”。
Vehicular autonomy, if perfected, could lead to much safer road conditions for all, lower insurance costs and enhance mobility for the elderly, the sick and those with disabilities.
如果车辆自动驾驶技术得到完善，可能会为所有人带来更安全的道路条件，更低的保险费用，并提高老年人、病人和残疾人的出行能力。
They would also allow roads to increase their capacity between 200 - 400%.
它们还可以使道路的通行能力提高200%至400%。
Perfection, though, seems to be just out of reach at the moment.
然而，目前看来，完美似乎还遥不可及。
To date Google's self-driving car, launched in 2012, has had 14 minor accidents.
到目前为止，谷歌在2012年推出的自动驾驶汽车已经发生了14起小事故。
Even worse, Tesla's Autopilot has caused one fatality in 2015, where the vehicle simply did not see the obstacle.
更糟糕的是，特斯拉的自动驾驶系统在2015年导致了一起死亡事故，当时车辆根本没有看到障碍物。
While the technology exists, driverless cars and full vehicular autonomy is still embryonic.
虽然这项技术已经存在，但无人驾驶汽车和完全的车辆自动驾驶仍然处于萌芽阶段。
That said, you can rest assured that further development in the field is inevitable.
话虽如此，可以放心的是，该领域的进一步发展是不可避免的。
And what's the future?
那么未来会怎样呢？
Well, George Marcus, co-founder of Geometric Intelligence — Uber's autonomous development department — imagines a world of flying cars taking us to work.
嗯，优步自动驾驶研发部门几何智能的联合创始人乔治·马库斯想象着一个有飞行汽车送我们去上班的世界。
He says "They're going to allow people to take long commutes at 75 or 150 mph where you'd otherwise get stuck in traffic.
他说：“它们将让人们能够以每小时75英里或150英里的速度进行长途通勤，否则你就会被困在交通堵塞中。
It's really, in a not-too-distant future, going to be something that is practical."
在不太遥远的未来，这真的会成为一种切实可行的方案。”
Wouldn't that be fine?
那不是很好吗？